英文字幕:
自动英文字幕
翻译: 谷歌翻译
校对，润色，压制:
Bolshevik0
Hi guys.
嗨 大家好
welcome back to the channel.
欢迎回到频道
Today we're gonna be checking out
今天我们看看
one of the most ridiculous user missions I've ever seen.
我见过的最荒谬的玩家自制任务之一
So remember April Fool's right
大家还记得愚人节吧
we had the submarines and they were doing tests I guess
有潜艇可以玩 我猜Gaijin又是在进行测试
with submarines etc for naval forces.
测试海战中的潜艇机制
I don't know if that will carry over into naval forces at all
我不知道这套机制以后是否会加入海战
but from the trend of April Fool's
不过根据以往愚人节的趋势
remember the pirate ships
还记得海盗船活动吗
we have boats now
而我们现在有船了
remember the Leopards and T-90s
还记得豹2A5和T-90吗
we have an abrams now
而我们现在有艾布拉姆斯了
so i believe that was the test
所以我相信那些都是测试
and don't get me wrong I enjoy tests
不要误会我的意思 我喜欢测试
but this year's April Fool's was more of a relaxed April Fool's
但今年的愚人节更像是一个轻松的愚人节
it got quite stale after a while
一段时间后它变得相当乏味
I mean with the squad of four it was quite enjoyable
我的意思是四个人开黑的话还是很有意思的
but again after a while it got a little stale
但玩了一段时间后 它变得有点乏味了
and with that said I hope they kind of go back to the more ridiculous April Fool's
我的意思是说我希望他们回到更愚蠢的愚人节
almost something along the lines of this
类似于现在要讲的这个东西
注:
这人ID的意思是玩游戏的时候不要生气.jpg 可以翻译成佛系_游戏
this is made by Nomad_Gaming
这是由Nomad_Gaming制作的
it's called ballistic missile simulator 2018
它被称为弹道导弹模拟器2018
this weak
这么弱的吗
these are the Trident
这些就是三叉戟弹道导弹
I'll hang on
等一下
I'll be quiet for a second.
我会安静一会儿
How many? 16 Trident missiles.
总共16枚三叉戟导弹
all in perfect engineering construction on the Katusha
经过如此精妙地工程学设计而放置在喀秋莎上面
this has to be one of these scariest views a human being could else...
这肯定是人类见过的最恐怖的情景之一
my gosh look 16 that Trident missiles staring you down
我的天哪你看 16个三叉戟导弹凝视着你.jpg
it looks like a giant spider
它看起来像一只巨大的蜘蛛
if you have or set phobia arachnophobia yeah well there you're too late now
如果你有蜘蛛恐惧症 那么你已经症状爆发了
sorry about that
对此我感到抱歉
but anyways Nomad has said that he has set the blast radius
但无论如何 制作者Nomad说他已经把爆炸半径设定在
for one of these tridents for or for these tridents
对于这些三叉戟
1.5 kilometer blast range with the TNT equivalent of 10,000 kilograms
1.5公里的爆炸范围 TNT相当于10,000千克
pretty much these things will kill anything you shoot
这些东西几乎会杀死你射击的任何东西
I mean anything and maybe some tanks down the way as well
我的意思是任何东西 也许能炸掉附近的别的坦克
we're gonna do a test-fire on this Maus here
我们会在这里对这个Maus做一个测试
on the way
准备
three two one
三二一
Oh fuck, we're getting faster.
哦 这个导弹变得更快
I don't really know what's happening guys oh god it's getting so fast
我真的不知道发生了什么 天啊 它变得如此之快
oh there oh we're off
哦 我们起飞了
we're taking off now there we go missile away
我们现在正在起飞 导弹正在离开大地
and we control it with the mouse
我们用鼠标控制它
let's burn some retro here
让我们在这里反推一下
Can we going off to the left a little bit we can go little more to the left
往左边一点
see Oh No missile missile lost missile loss abort abort
导弹丢失x2 中止x2
no no no balance it out balance it out
平衡它x2
there we go okay little more to the left
我们再往左走一点
so oh my gosh how high can we go with this thing let's just see if we can go
所以哦 我的天哪 我们可以有多高 让我们看看我们能不能
look let's go to space
飞到宇宙去
why am I losing altitude
为什么高度正在下降
吐槽:
你正在被土豆服务器吸住.jpg
I'm getting sucked down back into earth
我被吸回了地球
now I think it's maybe oh it's out of fuel
现在我想这可能是它的燃料不足
look at that very short rocket burn I think
我感觉这个火箭的推进时间太短了
I don't see any yucca yep this one's dead
好吧这一发用完了
well that was a blame explosion
这是一个失败的爆炸
okay we're gonna send this one up and then bring it back down
好的 我们会发射这个 然后让它返回
and see if we can hit this Maus over here
看看我们能不能在这里击中这个鼠式
on the way
准备
they're a much better launch good trajectory and down down down down down - down down
发射轨道更好 然后 赶快下降
beautiful hit
完美的命中
won't the panzer II showed up
二号坦克也被击毁了
oh man oh man okay we killed this Maus that Maus
哦天哪 我们杀了这个鼠式和那个鼠式
how are you still alive
我们用的这个载具怎么还能完好无损
on the way
准备
a Panzer 3 survived that
一辆3号坦克幸存了下来
there's no more trees
树木都被清光了
oh that was perfect ballistic missile simulator for the win
这一击真的完美 这是弹道导弹模拟器的胜利
oh man we could clear out a forest
哦 我们可以清除森林
there's absolutely no more trees around here
树木真的都消失了
let's see if we can clear this forest over here
让我们看看我们能否清除这个森林
this would be a much more effective way to build apartments
这也许是盖房子的一种更高效的方式
I'm still having to chop down every tree just send a Trident missile
只是发送一个三叉戟导弹 就不需要一棵棵地砍树了
Granny you probably couldn't have couldn't build there for a couple of decades
忽略掉这片地区数十年不能住人的问题
okay on the way or down we go
向下一击
did it clear them out oh yeah guys look at that
把那片树林全部清除了
it looks so all my FPS are actually improving right now
我的帧率现在在上升
but now let's launch one as high as we can
但现在让我们尽可能高的启动一个
oh my gosh
天啊
I don't it looks like a big ice cream bar
它看起来像一个大雪糕
up you go higher
仰角再大一下
this is as high as we can go
这个仰角已经是最大的了
launch one
发射一枚
okay bad bad launch but we were on the way
虽然起飞有些不顺利 但是已经在路上了
I wonder if we can get out into outer space
我想知道我们是否可以进入外太空
it doesn't take more in like six or seven minutes for one of these missiles I bet
我认为这些导弹进入到外太空的时间不超过六到七分钟
there's the ground below us we're definitely hitting Mach
大地正处于我们的下方 现在肯定接近音速了
maybe Mach two
也许有两倍音速
okay GPU is struggling to render or just the game limitations
好吧GPU正在努力渲染 或者只是游戏的限制
have less so just deleting the map right below us
没有那么复杂 只是删除我们下面的地图
the rocket is still firing we are still gaining altitude
火箭引擎仍在工作 高度仍在上升
we are in outer space no or not no
我们可能已经到了外太空
come on hold together don't go away oh it's getting smaller
不要就在这用尽燃料 加把劲 大地变得越来越小了
no no the view distance is getting smaller and smaller
不 视野距离越来越小
oh my I think
哦 我认为……
lots of lots of all faster reloading rate
装填速度真的很快
you go to the left a little bit this one will go to the right
这一发走左边 这一发走右边
it's Doomsday's boy doomsday boys
这是世界末日啊
oh my gosh this is like the end of the world right here
哦 我的天啊 这就像世界末日
two more left we have to reload
剩下两个我们必须重新装填
this reload will take so long
这个重新装填会花费很长时间
and down down below down below
往下飞往下飞
okay now I'm gonna crash this one just so I don't so I can go look at these things okay
好吧 现在我要把这发撞毁 这样我就可以回到喀秋莎视角看看这些导弹了
or we're going to this for... oh wow that looks absolutely terrifying
或者只是这样 看起来非常可怕
I just really wish that modelers could like beef up the explosion effects in this game
我真的希望建模者能够在这个自定义游戏中加强爆炸效果
because even right because I can't like it you know sure it has the blast radius and whatever
即使他做出了爆炸半径这些东西 我还是不太喜欢他的这个效果
but it doesn't show anything even when you drop like a 500-pound bomb
譬如500磅的炸弹的爆炸效果
compared to like even a pe8 a 5000 kilogram bomb
和佩8的5吨炸弹比起来
there's not well there is difference
还是有一定的区别
but it's not like that much more
虽然不是那么大的区别
like if you drop a 5 than be a better example if you drop a 500 pounder compared to a 1000
更好的例子譬如500磅炸弹对比1000磅
or even a 2,000
甚至2000磅
they look the same
爆炸效果看起来就像一样的
now the last thing that we have to do is we have to really simulate ballistic missile simulator
现在我们要做的最后一件事是 我们必须真正模拟弹道导弹
so we're going to have to take this raw launch this rocket
所以我们得按照最初的方式发射这个导弹
get it into a high enough altitude
让它进入足够高的高度
and bring it back down in the center of all these targets
并让它再回到这张地图的中心 打击所有这些目标
to be able to kill all with the 1 try that missile
能够用1枚导弹击毁所有目标
do that we're gonna launch and start turning right ASAP
为了做到这点 我们发射后就立刻右转
right there we go
那么开始吧
we got to burn as much or get as much turn as we can and while we're slow
尽管我们很缓慢 但还是需要尽可能地回转
because we're gonna start increasing speed by the second
因为我们的速度增长得实在太快了
ok
好
raise the altitude a little bit
提高一点点的高度
ok now where are we at looking at it
好的 我们现在在哪儿
oh gosh we're going so we're going so fast now
哦 天哪 我们正在远离目标 我们离开的速度现在有这么快
no no don't spin
别转
okay where are we
好的 我们在哪
you know there it is there it is
找到了
Oh get out of here bug
bug快离开
yes a little more to the right
没错 再偏右一些
and coming ballistic-missile
弹道导弹马上飞过来
door don't run out of fuel
别用完燃料
don't run out of fuel
don't run you running out of fuel
别用完燃料
you're out of fuel
燃料耗尽了
no I think I think we're turning in
不 我认为我认为我们正在向内转向
yes this was looking much better
是的 这看起来好多了
I don't know if we can yes hold together fuel
我不知道我们的燃料是否足够
a little bit more power
再加把劲
and we're gone on the other way
而我们却走了另一条路
okay 1.5 1.5
好 1.5 1.5
I don't know this will be closed
这就很接近了
missile down to the ground impact
导弹撞向地面 冲击
nothing
什么都没有发生
maybe the easiest way is just to launch it straight up just have it fall back down because of gravity
也许最简单的方法是直着发射它 让它因为重力而掉落下来
I mean I I've played Kerbal Space Program a little bit
我的意思是我玩过一点坎巴拉太空计划
okay little bit higher
再高一点
oh yeah this is definitely gonna work
哦 这个计划肯定会奏效
a little bit back -
再往回纠正一点
no it's not gonna work
不 它不会工作
a little bit more back
多回来一点
nope okay let's try to reverse the rocket here
没关系 好吧 让我们试着在这里回转火箭
up up up up
快点回转
oh we got it
哦 我们回来了
okay we were burning retro point seven away from the target point eight point nine
好吧 我们正在反推 4.7 4.8 4.9km
and we are closing I believe
我相信我们快要停止上升了
where is target
目标在哪里
target's right below target's right below
目标就在正下方
us look at the mini-map
看看小地图
yes
没错
no no no no go this way go this way go this way
不 不 不 走这条路
We still have fuel x2. This will be perfect.
我们仍然有燃料x2这将是完美的
Here's the heavy tank.
这是重型坦克
Where are the other vehicle? There's the another vehicle.
其他载具在哪里 还有另一辆载具
We're gonna kill one.
我们要击毁一辆
And can we got the panzer II?
我们能击毁二号坦克吗
Cut the Maus and that's about it.
击毁了鼠式 差不多就这些了
okay well we'll finish this, the less interesting way.
好吧 我们会通过不那么有趣的方式完成最后几发
Hey, you guys go.
嘿 你们走吧
Have one of them, apples.
击中其中一辆
That was pretty neat, wasn't it?
这确实很整齐
So once we let locked in the target, we can just like
所以我们一旦锁定了目标
launch another one and watch that one impact.
我们就可以发射另一个 并观察之前那发的结果
Okay now let's get the last one over here.
好的 现在让我们来看看最后一个
And there's still one more. This might kill him though.
还有一辆载具 虽然没有正中 但还是有可能击毁它
That should have got him.
这应该击毁它
Ad a little tap on the head.
轻轻地击中头部
Well we missed it.
不过我们错过了
Guys, if you want to check out this user made mission,
伙计们 如果你想查看这个用户自制任务
links in the description below.
可以在简介中找到链接
Nomad_Gaming, I encourage you to make more ridiculous stuff like this
Nomad_Gaming 我希望你制作更多像这样荒谬的东西
for us to see and to check out.
让我们好好玩玩看
Thank you for your time making this
感谢你为此付出的时间
and guys again I hope you have enjoyed this video.
同样 我也希望大家喜欢这个视频
Peace out.
再见